Guide to the Myron Gustin Fincher Papers, 1908-1993
Fincher, Myron Gustin papers, 1908-1993
- Series VIII. Cornell Office Files
  - 1949-1950
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Annual Conference for Veterinarians, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - B, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - B.A.I.-D.B.H. Dalrymple, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - B.A.I.-I.G. Howe, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - B.A.I.-E.V. Moore, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - B.A.I.-W.S. Stone, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Bristol Laboratories, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Budget-Ag. And Markets, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - C, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - D, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Day, Edmund E., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Delaval Separator Company, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Douglaston Manor, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - E, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - F, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Farquharson-Clinic Plans, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - G, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - H, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Hagan, W.A.-Mastitis reports, 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Annual reports to Dean Hagan, 1948-1950 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Hagan, W.A.-Mastitis reports, 1947-1948 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Heredity, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Harden Farms, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Holstein Historian, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - J, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Jenson-Salsbery Company, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Jurisprudence, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - K, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Kent, L.C., 1950 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - L, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Libraries-Cornell University, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Ledlerle Laboratories, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - M, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Masititis-Incomplete Surveys, Jan. 24, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - "An Approach to the Mastitis Problem" by M.G. Fincher, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - "An Approach to the Mastitis Problem", 1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - "An Approach to the Mastitis Problem", 1949 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "An Approach to the Mastitis Problem", 1949 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Canton Regional Mastitis Lab, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Earlville Regional Mastitis Lab, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - East Aurora Regional Mastitis Lab, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Farmingdale Regional Mastitis Lab, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Kingston Regional Mastitis Lab, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Veterinary Medical Department Projects, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Reports on Various Meetings Attended, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Bovine Mastitis paper, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Mc, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Murphy, James M., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - N, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - O, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Oneida Ltd., 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - P, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Photo Science Laboratory, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Pitman Moore Co., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - R, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Ring, Lawrence A., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Roberts, S.J., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - S, 1948-1950 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Sharpe and Dohme Inc., 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - E.R. Squibb & Sons, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Statler Club, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Syracuse Pharmacal Company, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - T, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Tucker, E.W., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - U, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - University Policy Committee, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Upjohn Co., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - V, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Veterinarians Wanted, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Vassar Formula, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Vibronic Abortion, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - W, 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Wallace Laboratories, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - XYZ, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - 1950-1951
    - A, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Atwood, S.S., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - B, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Beacon Milling Co., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - D.C. Blood, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Boardman, Donald A., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Bristol Laboratories, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - B.A.I.-Dalyrmple, D.B.H., 1950 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - B.A.I.-Howe, I.G., 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - B.A.I.-Moore, E.V., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Building Projects, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Building Projects, ca. 1951 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - New Vet. College Buildings, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - C, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - P.D. Camp Packing Co., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Conferences, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - D, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - D, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Davella Mills Foundation, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Day, Edmund E., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1951 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - E, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - F, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - G, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Granirer, Louis W., 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - H, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - H, 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1950-1951 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Hamilton Pharmaceutical Co., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Higley, P.I., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - H, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Horses, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Horse Papers & Types, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Hull, F.E., ca. 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - I, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - J, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Jackson, J.A.-General Cochran Farms, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Jensin-Salsbery Co., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - K, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Kent, L.C.-Letters, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Kings Park State Hospital, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Kirwin, William R., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - L, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - LaCroix, J.V., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Ledlerle Laboratories, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Letchworth Village Herd, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Cornell University Library, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - M, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Mc, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Mastitis Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Canton Regional Mastitis Lab, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - East Aurora Regional Mastitis Lab, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Kingston Regional Mastitis Lab, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Merk & Co., Inc, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Murphy, James M., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Mastitis-Basic Research, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Mastitis for Tennessee, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - N, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Neomycin, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - O, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Ortho Pharmaceutical Co., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - P, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Photo Science Laboratory, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Pitman-Moore Co., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Plastridge, W.N., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Poisonous Plants, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Poppensiek, G.C., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - R, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Roberts, S.J, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - S, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Sharp & Dohme, Inc, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - E.R. Squibb & Sons, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Statler Club, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - R.J. Strasenburgh Co., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - T, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Tarbells, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - U, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Upjohn Co., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - V, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Vibronic Abortion, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - W, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Wallace Laboratories, 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Winthrop-Stearns, Inc., 1950-1951 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Woelffer, E.A., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - XYZ, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - 1951-1952
    - A, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - A.V.M.A., 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - B, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Bristol Laboratories, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Building Project, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - C, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - P.D. Camp and Sons, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - D, 1950-1952 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Dewey, Thomas, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - E, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - F, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Fort Dodge Laboratory, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Fuerst Stock Farm, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - G, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Graduate School, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - H, 1951-1952 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Harden Farms, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Hamilton Pharmacal Co., 1951 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Haver-Glover Laboratories, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Higley, P.I., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Higley, P.I., 1952 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - I, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - J, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Jensen-Salsbery Laboratories, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Jackson, J.A.-General Cochran Farms, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - K, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Kent, L.C., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - NO FOLDER (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Kent, L.C.-Financial Statements, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Kings Park State Hospital, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - L, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Lederle Laboratories, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Leptospirosis, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - LaCroix, J.V., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - M, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Mc, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Canton Regional Mastitis Lab, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Earlville Regional Mastitis Lab, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Farmingdale Regional Mastitis Lab, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - East Aurora Regional Mastitis Lab, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Kingston Regional Mastitis Lab, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Merck and Co., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Meetings attended, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Murphy, J.M, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Annual Report, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - N, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinarians Medical Society, 1950-1952 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - O, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Ortho Research Foundation, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - P, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Parisitum Reprints, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Pitman-Moore Co., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Q-R, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - S, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Notes for Sterility Talks, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Sharpe & Dohme Inc., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - E.R. Squibbs & Sons, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - R.J. Strasenburgh Co., 1951 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - T, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Tucker, E.W., 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - U, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - University Policy Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Upjohn Co., 1951 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - V, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - W, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - C.V. Whitney Farms, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - XYZ, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - 1952-1953
    - A, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Annual Veterinary Conference, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Papers on antibiotics, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Annual Report material, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - B, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - B, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - B.A.I.-I.G. Howe, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - B.A.I. -E.V. Moore, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - B.A.I.-George Snook, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - B.A.I.-D.B. Dalrymple, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Bristol Laboratories, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - C, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Cortisone, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 70)
    - Annual Veterinarians Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 71)
    - Case Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Central; Islip State Hospital, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Cerophyl Labs, Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - D, 1955-1953 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1952 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - E, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - F, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Faculty, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Fluorine Examinations, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Fort Dodge Labs, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Fuerst Stock Farms, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - G, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Graduate School, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - H, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Hagan, W.G., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Annual Report, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Annual Report, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report material, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Hamilton Pharmacal Co., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Haver Glover Labs, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Harden Farms, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Higley, P.I., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - I, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - J, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Jensen Salsbery Labs, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - K, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Kent, L.C.-Financial Statements, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Kent, L.C., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - L, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Lederle Labs, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Library, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - M, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Mc, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Mastitis Annual Report, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Mastitis Panel, 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Mycoban, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Milking machines and mastitis, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Canton Regional Mastitis Lab, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Earlville Regional Mastitis Lab, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - East Aurora Regional Mastitis Lab, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Farmingdale Regional Mastitis Lab, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Kingston Regional Mastitis Lab, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Murphy, J.M., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Merck & Co., 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - N, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - NYS Veterinary College Alumni Association, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - NYS Veterinary Medical Society, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - O, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Ortho Pharmaceutical Co., 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - P, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Photo Science, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Pitman-Moore Co., 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Poppensiek, G.C., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Public Health Veterinarians, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - R, 1951-1952 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Roberts, S.J., 1952 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - S, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Sharp & Dohme, 1952-1954 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - E.R. Squibb & Sons, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - R.J. Strasenburgh Co, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - T, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Tucker, E.W., 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - U, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - University Policy Committee, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Upjohn Co., 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - V, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - XYZ, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - 1953
    - A, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Annual Report, 1952-1953 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Annual Veterinary Conference Papers, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - B, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Bristol Laboratories, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - C-D, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Chas. Pfizer and Co., Inc., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - E-F, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Faculty, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - G-H, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - H, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1953-1954 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - I, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - J, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - K, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - L, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - M, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Canton Regional Mastitis Lab, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Earlville Regional Mastitis Lab, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - East Aurora Regional Mastitis Lab, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Farmingdale Regional Mastitis Lab, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Kingston Regional Mastitis Lab, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Milking Machines, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Mastitis Reports, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - N, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - O-P, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - P, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - R, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - S, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - S, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - T, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - U-V, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - W, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - 1954-1955
    - Correspondence A, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Admissions, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - "Herds Serviced by Ambulatory Test for Bangs and T.B. Tests", 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - The American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - American Breeder's Service, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association-Borden Award, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Annual Veterinary Conference, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Abbott and Armour Laboratories, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - B, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - B, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - B, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - N.Y.S. Department of Agriculture-Bureau of Animal Industry
      - Correspondence to I.G. Howe, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence to D.B.H. Dalrymple, 1950-1955 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence to E.V. Moore, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence to George Snook, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence to W.S. Stone, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Bristol Laboratories, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Baird Farms Bulls, May-June, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - C, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Camp Packing Co., 1954 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Case Reports, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Collections, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Collections, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - D, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Gov. Thomas E. Dewey, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - E, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - F, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Faculty, Committees, etc., 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - 1st World Congress on Fertility and Sterility, 1953-1954 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - 1st World Congress on Fertility and Sterility, 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - 1st World Congress on Fertility and Sterility, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - G, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Fort Dodge Laboratory, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Fuerst Stock Farm, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Harden Farms, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Graduate School and Students, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - H, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - H, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Hagan, W.A., June 4, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Discussion with W.A. Hagan, June 4, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Requests for W.A. Hagan, May 5, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report; Medical Department Staff to W.A. Hagan, Apr.-June 1954 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Harrision Stocks (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Hamilton Pharmacal Company Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Harris vs. Miller, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Haver-Glover Laboratories, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - H.G. Hodges, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - H.G. Hodges, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - I, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - J, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - J.W. Jackson; General Cochran Farms, 1953-1955 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Jenson-Salsbery Laboratories, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - K, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - L.C. Kent, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - King's Park State Hospital, 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - J.V. Lacroix, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - J.V. Lacroix, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - L, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - L, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Lederle Laboratories, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Veterinary Library, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - M, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Memos to field Veterinarians, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Dr. Migale's Experiment (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Dr. G.E. Morse, Director of Laboratories, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Machold Farms, 1952-1954 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Mahrapo Farms, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Mahrapo Farms, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Mahrapo Farms, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Mastitis-Central Office, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Dibenzylamine Penicillin "G", 1953 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Regional Mastitis Lab-Canton, NY, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Regional Mastitis Lab-Earlville, NY, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Regional Mastitis Lab-Kingston, NY, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - East Aurora, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Meetings attended, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Meetings attended, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Merk and Company, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - J.M. Murphy, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - N, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - O, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - P, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Reclassification of Public Health Veterinarians, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Outline of Procedure for Conducting Physical Examination of Daily Herds, 1953-1954 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Revision of Sanitary Code, 1952-1954 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Public Health Relations Committee of the N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Meetings in Moore Lab, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - N.Y.S.P.H.R.C.-Rabies, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - N.Y.S.P.H.R.C.-Rabies, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Fred Shutz and Carol Paterno, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Herds Sent in by Dr. V.J. Peppe, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Photo Science, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Pitman-Moore Company, 1953-1955 (Box 19, Folder 13)